(Sheldon:)73 is the 21st prime number.
(Sheldon:)Its mirror, 37, is the 12th,
and its mirror, 21,
(Sheldon:)is the product of multiplying--
(Sheldon:)hang on to your hats--
seven and three.
(Sheldon:)Eh? Eh? Did I lie?
(Leonard:)We get it.
(Leonard:)73 is the Chuck Norris
of numbers.
(Sheldon:)Chuck Norris wishes.
In binary 73 is a palindrome:
"one-zero-zero-
one-zero-zero-one"
which backwards is "one-zero-
zero-one-zero-zero-one"--
(Sheldon:)exactly the same.
(Sheldon:)All Chuck Norris backwards
gets you is: "Sirron Kcuhc."
(Raj:)Just for the record,
when you enter 5,318,008
on a calculator,
upside-down it spells "boobies""
(Leonard:)Remember when you were wondering
(Leonard:)why the girls didn't
want to eat with us tonight?
(Howard:)Yeah, I get it now.
(Penny:)I love your little
heart locket, Bernadette.
(Bernadette:)Oh, thanks.
(Bernadette:)Howard gave it to me.